https://www.everyschool.com/privacy-policy/

0
was successfully added to your cart.
No menu assigned!
Everyschool.com Privacy Policy
Everyschool.com and the Campus Alliance is committed to respecting your privacy. We do not rent or sell our email lists or personal email information of any type. Your email address may be used to notify you of ministry ideas, events or products. You may opt out of these mailings at any time. For more detailed information, see below.
The Information We Collect
We do not collect personally identifiable information on our Site unless you voluntarily provide such information about yourself via an electronic mail message or by filling out one of our online forms. On our Site, you can adopt your school, subscribe to our email newsletter, post messages to our message board, and upload videos, articles and pictures. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and fax number. If you send us an email, we may use the information you provide to follow up via telephone or email. The information you provide will be kept confidential and will be used only to support your continued relationship with everyschool.com and the Campus Alliance.
No software or hardware techniques are employed to capture a visitor’s email address or other personally identifiable information. Everyschool.com does not monitor individual traffic patterns on our Site, and we do not use “cookies” or invisible images to track how you use our Site. Our hosting company may collect anonymous, aggregate information or statistics related to Site usage. These statistics indicate the total number of hits, the total number of page hits, the number of kilobytes transferred from our Site, and the IP address of the visitor. We may have the ability to access this information, but have chosen not to avail ourselves of this data. If we decide to use this information to analyze Web traffic in the future, we will only be able to measure the number of visitors to our Site and the addresses of the Web sites from which our visitors come. Email addresses and other personally identifiable information are not available to us.
How the Information You Provide Is Used
We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our services, to respond to your inquiries or questions, and to offer you helpful information about campus ministry, adopting your school and outreach that we believe may be of interest to you.
The information we collect in connection with our online forums is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums. As any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public, caution should be exercised when disclosing personal information.
We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.
Should you send us your comments or questions via email to any email address provided on our Site, we will only share your communications with our employees or agents most capable of addressing your questions and concerns. We will retain your communication until we have done our very best to provide you with a complete and satisfactory response and then we will either discard it or archive it. We will only disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. We do not sell, rent or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information you may provide without your consent.
Security of Information Sent to Us
Please note that, unless we expressly advise you otherwise, the email functionality on our Site does not provide a means for completely secure and private communications between us. Like all unencrypted Internet email communications, your email may be accessed and viewed by other Internet users, without your knowledge and permission, while in transit to us. For that reason, to protect your privacy, please do not use email to communicate information to us that you consider to be confidential. While we strive to protect your personal information, Everyschool.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we will use our commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our internal systems. Depending on the nature of the inquiry, your communication may be discarded or archived. If you wish, you may contact us instead via the mailing address on the bottom of each page on the site.
Privacy Policies of Web Sites Not Under Our Control
For your convenience, this Site may provide links to various Web sites that we do not control. When you click on one of these links, you will be transferred out of our Site and connected to the Web site of the organization or company that you selected. We are not responsible for the nature, quality or accuracy of the content or opinions expressed in such Web sites, and such Web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked for quality, accuracy or completeness by us. Inclusion of any linked Web site on the everyschool.com Site does not imply or express an approval or endorsement of the linked Web site by us, or of any of the content, opinions, products or services provided on these Web sites. Even if an affiliation exists between our Site and a third-party Web site, we exercise no control over linked sites. Each of these linked sites maintains its own independent privacy and data collection policies and procedures. If you visit a Web site that is linked to from our Site, we encourage you to consult that Web site’s privacy policy before providing any personal information and whenever interacting with any Web site.
Access and Correction
You have a right to know about the personal information that everyschool.com has collected through your requests as describe above, including the right to correct, amend or delete the information that everyschool.com has on file if it is incorrect. You may also change the status of whether you wish to receive everyschool.com alerts, newsletters and communications at any time. If at any time you wish to exercise these rights, feel free contact us by email.
Modifications to This Privacy Policy
Please bear in mind that we may change the content or design of our Site, and consequently, this Policy at any time in the future. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this page. You are responsible for reviewing this Policy periodically, and your continued use of our Site following any modifications to this Policy will be conclusively deemed acceptance of any changes.
Everyschool.com welcomes comments and questions about this Policy and about our Site. We are dedicated to protecting your personal information while providing a robust and friendly Web environment. Any comments or questions regarding everyschool.com electronic information privacy practices may be directed to our Webmasters via email. You may also send a letter to:
Campus Alliance
Everyschool.com
PO Box 28342
San Diego, CA 92198
Adopt Your School
Adopt Your School
Share Your Experience
Together
Prayer is Huge!
Get more stuff like this in your inbox
Subscribe to our mailing list and get interesting stuff and updates to your email inbox.
we respect your privacy and take protecting it seriously
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Contact
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
© 2020 Every Student Every School. All Rights Reserved.
